<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>¡Kay Bueno!</title>
    <description></description>      
    <link>http://www.kaybueno.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kaybueno.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I’ve been MIA this week</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Being off routine is hard. And I’ve been out of whack this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I flew Monday night into Baltimore. Drove to Maryland. Slept for 4 hours, and then woke up to interview a bunch of awesome students. The campus was gorgeous&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/uJv3RlnS1it3oYHYZRGTuHXcscFOxEIGOYvROXTec00=w707-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/Oc0_UvKVCM-9A-JmSpENM11UB1EkjU7dkmE9BEQu_Ek=w980-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finally felt like I was experiencing fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I flew back Wednesday and had a lot of work waiting for me. I’ve basically been holed up at my desk and home until today when I helped with the company Halloween party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/QUkuFwp9oNoOEC8oRpm1-2Cq3_dG5zhct5toSqgO1Jo=w1038-h607-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-8lBt9llc6aw/VFMea9EvDqI/AAAAAAAAMv8/6Fa89jLQV2E/w955-h716-no/IMG_4148.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m putting together a last minute zombie costume. (Oh god)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/ypQXQHDhJQYLsLtzWVWDVwrOjl0KtjKilkOpygokiQ0=w501-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mixing up some fake blood as we speak. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your weekend plans? Halloween parties anyone?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-30-2014/MIA.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-30-2014/MIA.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Run 10 Feed 10 recap</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Spoiler alert. I ran Run 10 Feed 10, and I was bad. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s start from the beginning though. I woke up at 6 am to get ready for this race. I had carefully prepared all the things I needed the night before. However, my morning brain couldn&amp;#39;t remember where I put them. So I spent like half an hour freaking out and looking for them. Good going Kay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I pulled myself together, and hauled myself to Crissy Field. I was pumped. The views were beautiful. There were a ton of runners. It was good. I started snapping some quick pictures from the field of the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-JLSTgjLKqvw/VE01Eoh6K5I/AAAAAAAAMdA/4GcCJDtqWNM/w955-h716-no/IMG_4068.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate subtle foreshadowing, so I&amp;#39;m going to be obvious here. The bridge looks pretty high up from where I was taking photos. I thought nothing of that at the time. The morning was beautiful, there were cute booths. I got to put on a temporary tattoo and got prizes for taking selfies (basically my dream). The world was good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/oPjIXWqMXULk-fHw8WGbMWHrYd6C5QZ2BOtZRre4r88=s716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Women&amp;#39;s Health put on a killer display. There were a bunch of adorable sponsor booths. We warmed up with a very calm instructor from a local yoga studio. They had tons of photographers coming around snapping pictures, making me feel like people should always be taking pictures of my pre-run festivities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They lined up the runners into different pace groups. I wanted this to be a chill run, and didn&amp;#39;t want to feel super competitive (I did this run to take pictures of the bridge!) So I put myself in the last group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/xb6nh2Ig8Cy7LDBk8DucHLSOfwyxFFLHAYJgAwQ2AcI=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And we started! There wasn&amp;#39;t a lot of fanfare for this. I hit the button on my cheapo Garmin, and started my playlist that I haven&amp;#39;t updated since Seawheeze and started running. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The photos of the bridge, are pretty killer. And the road was blocked off, so I didn&amp;#39;t feel overcrowded or anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/g6CTli4YXS60_cK1vMpZad5XyBSXcqSPX6DzwCg5Mis=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-L5PVajP060w/VE01S6Jb9sI/AAAAAAAAMfA/loE2VqAxrW4/w955-h716-no/IMG_4079.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However. This route starts with a whole lot of uphill. Annnd. Elevation and I aren&amp;#39;t friends. Furthermore, if you know how a bridge works, it&amp;#39;s basically sloping up and down the entire way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my recent runs, I haven&amp;#39;t been feeling any fatigue until mile 5 or so. On this run, 2 miles in and I was gross. Sweaty, and breathing heavy, and a real mess. While they had water at the other end of the bridge, there were not enough water stations in the world to fix and hydrate me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finished the race at an embarrassing 10:30 pace. And looked something like this at the end:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-JsWryTDmHFc/VE01ZY_WriI/AAAAAAAAMf8/Ycs-CFV6urs/w537-h716-no/IMG_4090.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could give you the 150 excuses I have for a bad run. But it really boils down to lack of practice. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said. Run 10 Feed 10 was beautiful, and amazing. And if you get the chance to run over the Golden Gate Bridge, you should DEFINITELY do it. At the end there was a delicious bagel and fruit spread, dynamic stretching (I waited 30 minutes in line for this and it was worth every second), and a great yoga session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-QHi6BTmArYk/VE01FndeOtI/AAAAAAAAMdI/1wjQ94KrAMY/w955-h716-no/IMG_4069.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please, tell me of your successes this weekend. I went to the Bridge School Benefit after this, and got to feel really good about my fitbit step count all day. So all in all, not bad. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-27-2014/run10feed10.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-27-2014/run10feed10.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I&#39;m becoming a bag lady</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was one of those days that started with the water heater not working. Unfortunately, when you’re trying to wash your hair as infrequently as possible (for its own health!) and you’re on day four or five. You have to shower. Needless to say, my day didn’t begin on a great note.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was packet pickup for Run 10 Feed 10, which is a 10k by Women’s Health that crosses the Golden Gate Bridge. I’ve only ever crossed via car, and I love trashy health magazines. So J and I walked to the running store to pick up my packet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/5_WXeAHPHW6KLkHkd8fT4pquxQxePo8tJr32dEPlCtE=w1038-h684-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that it’s November, we scrambled out in tshirts because the weather here is still in the 70s. It’s crazy. Halloween is in a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-aWwc5m7Lyg0/VEwgXHVRWcI/AAAAAAAAMag/I7F_2koYoyI/w931-h716-no/IMG_4055.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Run 10 Feed 10 bag was adorable. But hilariously, I’m most excited for the temporary tattoos. I missed doing the “Run Yoga Party” spray on tattoos for Seawheeze and so I’m making up for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ended up with another free bag for Google Shopping Express (a same day delivery service in the Bay). Their logo is a parachute, and so they sent out these adorable themed bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-KKPCJfw6hqQ/VEwgMsKkbII/AAAAAAAAMXo/WZ4m3CEu6QI/w537-h716-no/IMG_4049.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reusable bags are a pretty big deal here, since it costs 10 cents to buy disposable bags at any store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got home we had already walked a bunch around the city. So I snapchatted my family really attractive faces while J worked. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-FNcJqtnk2Lw/VEwgbE_drXI/AAAAAAAAMZU/0jfKn9dQfO4/w537-h716-no/IMG_4058.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got dinner plans and an early bedtime waiting for me tonight. (Race starts at 7:30ish) Eugggh. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the best swag you ever got? (I hope it’s not temporary tattoos, otherwise, we gotta talk.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-25-2014/bag-lady.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-25-2014/bag-lady.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Work work work</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;No real update today babes. I had one of those days at work where you’re cranking things out so hard that you don’t realize you’ve been there ten hours. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend is going to be a straight up blast though. Women’s Health 10k, on Sunday, and Bridge School Benefit too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only adorable part of my day came in the form of lunch. Work was celebrating breast cancer awareness. So they did a beet paper (pink) wrapped sushi roll. With a salad, and some indian inspired cabbage dish, they were a pretty fantastic lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/WuMLVMW0au8cTH9IOMovY93FnGZ2-xaikS0p_jFumIM=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/3XUEBMMyqKezCVQ-YHlr_W9eMhPbvQy1wdhPt6u8zGk=w1038-h582-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How was your weekend shaping up? Any major plans?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-24-2014/work.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-24-2014/work.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s your motivation?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At 5:30 pm, after a 9 hour day of standing (I have a lovely standing desk), looking at a computer screen, and typing, the last thing I want to do is go run, or exercise in general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then my brain starts telling me. “Oh, you don’t need to run. You have… work. You’re… tired. You could… spend this time better.” And it takes a lot of work, some will power and a few tricks to get myself here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/3f1JmkMPH6r8vXm5xiiDYymZwE3rDdIYEdxI9f6XLKg=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Seriously this is one of the few times I cared enough in the morning to put on matching socks. Usually I have like, one lime sock and one purple one.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working on a few tricks to get myself to keep ignoring the lazy person inside of me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buy myself things for doing exercise. Childish perhaps. And consumeristic, but very effective. Usually, I set some sort of goal, like: “Exercise 5 days this week”. This week (given I work out tomorrow) I’m buying &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.etsy.com/listing/167820434/day-of-the-dead-boston-terrier-sugar&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-piTRIVkYqxQ/VEm-JxvgxFI/AAAAAAAAMVw/FLjZze7szn0/w570-h544-no/diadelosdog.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep everything I need to workout at my desk. Everyone in my building has a little file cabinet. And while most people keep extra work supplies in them (one of my coworkers keeps his full of listerine), I keep a bunch of shirts, a spare pair of tennis shoes, socks and hairbands in them. So I can always get from work appropriate to workout appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-KEi93M6r840/U-KsUJ8tcrI/AAAAAAAAE2k/H9NScVWwhrc/w537-h716-no/IMG_1863.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Things I wouldn’t mind putting in my file cabinet. If I had more money, and I trekked up the the Nike store more often.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brag. No one likes the self righteous exerciser. But I have a few key friends who put up with my boasting because they know if I keep up on staying fit, I’m a more sane person. And I’m always open to them when they want to hit me up about their latest sweat sesh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even with all of this, sometimes fitness still falls by the wayside. What’s your trick to keeping motivated?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-23-2014/motivation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-23-2014/motivation.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What I ate Wednesday</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have to say, while I usually don’t love looking at my own mediocre pictures of food that I secretly take while (I hope) my coworkers aren’t looking. I get some perverse joy out of seeing what other people are eating, and so in that, I have to indulge you in my Wednesday food lineup. If you too love looking at what others are eating check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://peasandcrayons.com/&quot;&gt;more here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is food no filter. So what I ate, I snapped. Basically, all my meals are provided by my workplace. So I’m a little constrained with what I eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/TJJMFn1QlUzjpfCuBH3DXkXqBDnOY3uJ0lLhYfVIBFA=w890-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breakfast is usually fruit + eggs or cottage cheese. (Plus a giant coffee, black). This is just the most simple meal that will tide me over until lunch. I have this basically every day but Friday. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MfHRSq3-7l4/VEgCW9NYkEI/AAAAAAAAMSE/H7LNXJd4D2A/w955-h716-no/IMG_4034.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a food truck here today that served salads!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-aSb6075UWVw/VEgCeFI6DhI/AAAAAAAAMTA/pe7EZep8nlY/w955-h716-no/IMG_4039.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tuna poke salad with carrots, cucumbers, brown rice and a miso dressing. Super delicious but, way too much rice. My bowl looked like this at the end of lunch:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-52GhPzAC0A4/VEgEF-Cx3pI/AAAAAAAAMUs/7N5S-KdmzGs/w875-h716-no/IMG_4040.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a person who lives off of snacks. So in the afternoon, I had a little of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-pU8tj7pG63c/VEfmprnQHvI/AAAAAAAAMUQ/0ZaKsmMxD3w/w604-h716-no/IMG_4028.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And some of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/XgrbgZ6rEWWi411MZwXCIOK0VHmQmccHA2lUm-TxMfQ=w537-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not much of a dinner person, so taking one from Oliva Pope, I’ll be having a bowl of popcorn, but no wine. I’d snap a picture, but I haven’t eaten it yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over all, I’d probably like to add some more vegetables to my day, and maybe a little protein. I’m hoping to pick up some Quest bars on the suggestion of a friend, because while my body handles sugar substitutes pretty well, I become a maniac on sugar. Maybe next Wednesday I’ll throw in a real salad. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In true form, I can’t end this post without this awesome and hilariously flattering selfie I took and then applied a million filters to this morning. My toggling with weird image settings game is getting so strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-UoHEEtxeCSk/VEfmnrmhYlI/AAAAAAAAMU0/tiR8ErMnqQk/w438-h716-no/IMG_4026.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know pumpkin is like the it food of the month. I obviously need to work on my pumpkin game. Have you been indulging in any fall favorites?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-22-2014/WIAW.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-22-2014/WIAW.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How I’m improving for Seawheeze 2015.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Seawheeze 2014 was one of the best experiences of my life. It was my first half marathon. I was able to travel to Vancouver to do a beautiful run. I was so in love with it, I signed up only a month after finishing, just to run it again this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-eLhyEkexHl0/U-KbONyZxWI/AAAAAAAADgI/g644W8tVHFk/s716-no/IMG_1567.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Run selfie&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That said, it was my first half, and there are a lot of things I’d like to improve on the next time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Run other races. Seawheeze was my first half marathon, but it was also my first real race. I didn’t start running until 14 weeks before the race, and unfortunately, I couldn’t even fit a real, organized 5k in before it. But this year, I’m running a bunch of different races. I figure, it’s good to figure out how the whole race circus works before you run 13 miles of one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/--IGr8r8VJnA/U-Ki8-ohixI/AAAAAAAAEM4/j4mgzjUiJ6k/w640-h617-no/IMG_1591.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Train early. While I’m perversely proud that I went from couch to half marathon in a little under 4 months, I think it’s a pretty crazy goal if you aren’t incredibly devoted. I’m excited to have time to improve upon my runs, not just knock out specific mileage in hopes of hitting 13 of them by a certain date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cross train. The app strongly suggests yoga and cross training alongside the running. As a naive, but busy person. I figured. I’m running a race, I just need the running part. So I skipped all the suggested yoga, and cross training, and just ran. This caused a lot of unnecessary tightness, and pain, and if I was more of an idiot, potential injury.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-S3xLpftBP7M/VEWLBo8yDbI/AAAAAAAAMN4/IZrL6rrVwhk/w403-h715-no/IMG_4018.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Train outdoors more. I love, and will make every argument for treadmill running. I can set a pace, turn off my brain, watch bad reality tv on my phone, and put a giant fan on myself since I sweat more than anyone I know. But! If you’re going to run outside, you might want to do some outside runs. I’m hoping to fit more in, or find someone to run with in the park. (And yes, I do photograph my silly treadmill runs.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TtsJz_VVYeM/U-KwtL-q_oI/AAAAAAAAMOU/Guj6MM381Fk/w1038-h658-no/IMG_2079.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even with my newbie mistakes, signing up to run a half marathon on a whim was one of the best things I could have ever done. I’m just hoping to document my gaffes so I don’t let it happen twice. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any half marathon, or just running tips you learned the hard way?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-21-2014/improving-seawheeze.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-21-2014/improving-seawheeze.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Art is everywhere! Sunday’s recap</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I read on Friday night that Adobe was unveiling a new mural in our neighborhood at 8 am Saturday morning. However, there was no way I was going to get J up before noon to look at one mural. (Heaviest. Sleeper. Alive.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So on Sunday after brunch we stopped by to get a look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Bfiy7YORjd5YW-u9A0-8N92C92z7vizWVNk9mjAdRs=w874-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal, if I remember correctly, is to spark creative moments for passers by. The artist figures people keep their heads down and ignore their surroundings when they walk, and murals like these make you take notice of your surroundings. People were definitely noticing it when we were there, there was practically a queue waiting to snap photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mural is in a larger “park” area, that often holds fitness classes, has super adorable coffee and juice bars, and is generally a fun place to explore. And so we did!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fitness section had some serious monkey bars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-BnsuXs5clUs/VEQhzThqV-I/AAAAAAAAMJ4/CtTdY8Oukiw/w537-h716-no/IMG_4003.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;J on monkey bars&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J did them with ease. I tried, but it was a total failure. Since most monkey bars are in parks for kids, I always have the safety net of being able to put my feet down. But these were definitely designed with adults in mind. Both J and I had to seriously hop to grab. On the first bar my sweaty palms slipped right off. One day I’m going to go back with some chalk and more resolve, and try again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last installation was this bucket list inspired piece: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/USoJl9xSababi32xk-ViL0UZf0rWLsDmSzvHcJrhayk=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/bWidfx-XZD_sw9aIhh9D-TmdIP35eMCNYrx72nYF1HY=w940-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved some of the answers, like: “Do a barrel roll.” or “Kiss someone I love in the rain” or “Help beat cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s silly, but one of the more frivolous goals I have is to be able to do the splits. I didn’t put it on the board, and I’m not sure that it’s something I need to do before I die. But seeing what everyone else has on their bucket list made me think of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s something you want to do before you die?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-20-2014/art-everywhere.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-20-2014/art-everywhere.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Awww, shucks.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Growing up in the midwest, I’m not particularly accustomed to seafood outside of fish, and maybe shrimp in a cocktail. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when a good friend was having her birthday at a state park, two hours north of San Francisco, where the plan was to shuck oysters. I was pumped! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And petrified. I’ve never taken a shell off of anything more than a hermit crab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The location was beautiful. To be fair, every beach in California is beautiful, but Point Reyes really has some amazing shoreline views. J and I hiked (if you can call it that) up a short paved cliffside road to watch some surfers and enjoy the view before the other party-goers got there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-rkS27TFvE80/VEMFAEjwjGI/AAAAAAAAMEA/6ZcpuIdQzFk/w955-h716-no/IMG_3942.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-CXTI6SwZFi8/VEMCDr4tu0I/AAAAAAAAMCk/x8hWE1_jy5s/w955-h716-no/IMG_3923.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 20 people came, a pretty good turn out for a seaside birthday. Unfortunately, the most familiarity anyone in the group had with shucking oysters was a few YouTube videos. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, both sea otters and gulls are pretty good at getting oysters open. So we figured a few 20 somethings with knives couldn’t do too poorly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/CcaP5WI4p5HR4fZxtbm5KyT3vd03UIZHy4wDlid00iY=w680-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/VPYqwIhuHBV5a3i4nBkx3eApZWYmaq68Rz1wo2UEkS8=w622-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After success with the first mollusc, everyone wanted to get their hands on one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/Tc3Fa-vnu_5UsL8U0VJA1ehdMl6bhPzk4KfFbgCHvrI=w1037-h601-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had 100 oysters, a bunch of sides, and some gorgeous picnic tables laid out by the beach. Turns out, even for a midwestener, getting oysters out of their shells isn’t very difficult, and eating them fresh with a little lemon and hot sauce is one of the best things ever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/fPGy6Vpys5B7JjxUXCEFc6tucdn4zEmWGCRq990SbUE=w570-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friends, sun, sand and sea were the perfect way to spend a Saturday morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How’s your weekend going? Try anything new recently?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bloglovin.com/blog/13035793/?claim=39h7sw2bze6&quot;&gt;Follow my blog with Bloglovin!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-18-2014/shucks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-18-2014/shucks.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Friday Favessss.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My mailbox has had a pretty awesome week of packages, and so I wanted to share all the great things I got this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team at work just launched, and so to celebrate we got t-shirts (and also went out for beers and appetizers.). Usually, shirts from work are the type of thing you only ever want to wear to sleep, or work out in. This one actually looks kind of okay (if you disregard the serious duck face I’m giving. Haha.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-7nCyC0pfUJ8/VEG80m0NoCI/AAAAAAAAL-o/FgfKRu6LAYY/w537-h716-no/IMG_3903.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an addict for subscriptions, and one of the lesser known ones I love is &lt;a href=&quot;http://footcardigan.com/&quot;&gt;Foot Cardigan&lt;/a&gt;. They send you an adorable pair of socks monthly. Both J and I have a subscription, and they’re awesome because, who doesn’t wear socks? Granted, few people see them except when I’ve got my pants cuffed to bike to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This month’s festive pair is so adorable though. ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/nBAuTLZjZ6GfkDFcivjSZCnIpj9KdQEBJL0OOyrkTp8=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I buy waaaaay too many cards. While I keep pretty light on spending usually, I am basically a card hoarder. Fortunately, it comes in handy when you find out you’re going to a birthday with only a few days notice. This one is super adorable and kitschy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YgTuE4yHgWw/VEHaHV3thKI/AAAAAAAAL_U/bX2TQQ9P_Og/w537-h716-no/IMG_3912.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last, but not least. Shoes! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in first grade and a student wore new shoes to class, the teacher would let you stand on your desk, and then almost as if singing happy birthday, or saying the pledge, all the other students would say in tandem “Ooooh, ahhhh, neeeew, shoooes.” It was a great way to start a healthy shoe addiction young.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the VivoBarefoot ones. The boyfriend has been super into minimalist traveling, and so he convinced me into trying a pair of barefoot shoes. They’re incredibly light, and only have a 4 mm base, which makes me less of a giant. I’m pretty addicted to my Mizunos, but I’ll be giving these a try this week. It&amp;#39;s definitely a different feel from cushy shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/i4jcycKLfXM749LaDzSnfDrjzYlq60orF3QfNSb0AEc=w693-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/ZzorMvSvpTfghrp1YUCjHRib13P58-OTia5PT153FO8=s672-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any big plans for the weekend? Got any faves from this week?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-17-2014/friday-faves.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-17-2014/friday-faves.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Woooah, it&#39;s fall.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Up until today, my life still felt like summer. California has been bright, sunny, and warm. I had yet to bundle up in anything more than a t-shirt. Heck, even the trees were still bright green.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But today, that all changed! Now, it’s unquestionably fall. And it all began with a pumpkin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-zyYtyfJV3M0/VECHHx2RjqI/AAAAAAAAL4o/jKQ34uBCFcE/s716-no/IMG_3896.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 1600 pound pumpkin for that matter. Someone had delivered it to the office, and it was as tall as me (and I’m 5’10”.) And just… giant. All I could think of is how many muffins, scones, and spice lattes you could make with that sucker. Delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, at lunch, I got roped into (read: I totally volunteered for) making decorations for my company’s Halloween party. It’s Alice in Wonderland themed (isn’t that the best? Spooky and whimsical without being cliche). So today I helped fold some of 800 paper roses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-e0VbHCYZ4pU/VECHK6cMIyI/AAAAAAAAL7A/h9EWMwH_OWY/w955-h716-no/IMG_3894.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZF2V5EM3i-8/VECHMOCKi6I/AAAAAAAAL60/68CytVOVMYg/w756-h716-no/IMG_3895.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Folding was a nice break from my typical daily work. The directions were super easy, and surprisingly, despite a bunch of us all working at once, the flowers turned out great. &lt;a href=&quot;http://pldevents.com/how-to-paper-flowers/&quot;&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; is basically exactly what we did. Everyone at the table kept remarking that it felt like they were crafting for their wedding all over again, and how much they missed the DIY aspect of planning for it. By lunch end, we had knocked out about 100. The Queen’s maze is going to look great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Decorating for Halloween and giant pumpkins started getting me in the fall mood. But then I walked into yoga tonight, and the class door was open to the outside, and it was freezing. Finally the temperature was telling me something. It’s fall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-EZoSRD1DDwo/VECHNSPdIFI/AAAAAAAAL6k/43k4kG1bioA/w999-h716-no/IMG_3897.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We closed the door and got to class. This yoga is called “Creative Yoga and Flow”, and it&amp;#39;s the first yoga class I ever took. The first time I took from this instructor, when she was fixing my form, she gasped and cried out (to the entired class) “You need yoga! Your muscles are so tight. You work out too much with no yoga.” While simultaneously flattering (I work out!) and embarrassing (omg did everyone hear that), her class has been great for me to deepen my stretches in the basic poses. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-_bgZZCOtseE/VECHQI9fotI/AAAAAAAAL6s/_KwG6uo6btk/w906-h716-no/IMG_3899.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, I’m ready with my mat, block and strap, well before the class starts. I can’t lie, I like to be on time. But my biggest pet peeve, is people who walk in late. 5-10 minutes late? Totally fine. 30-45 minutes late in an hour and fifteen minute class. Ridiculous. By that point, I’m in the middle of class, holding a pose, and the student who just walked in is asking me to move. Totally throws me off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How’s your day been? Feeling fall? And what’s your biggest pet peeve?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-16-2014/woah-fall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-16-2014/woah-fall.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Day 6 - The end of Hawaii :(</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On the Big Island, we stayed in the cutest B&amp;amp;B right outside Volcanoes National Park. Bamboo Orchid Cottage is basically a giant house buried in the middle of (what feels like) the rainforest. The owner is fantastically fun, and takes great care of the place, when we came in after hiking, the fireplace was lit, a soothing CD was on, and the room smelled amazing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But my favorite part was the breakfast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/tNAA6yV3qOsxM6g69jd01eCI6kOJrwSlnqU3OxhtkZA=w845-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The owner made us all lobster shaped papaya boats! The fruit on Hawaii was so fresh that I could have eaten two of these every morning. So delicious. My other favorite (and one of the only things I bought in Hawaii) was this adorable running shirt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/D5jpeMh3ztJPMks3VI0dszMP2Eng2_wQ101seD9I8lM=w537-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The store was so cute, and when we walked by I had to run in and have it. Had to. I can’t wait to do a race in this sucker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We spent some time hiking Akaka Falls, hiking is a strong word as it’s just a tiny loop. But unlike in Maui, the falls here had water! It was a beautiful destination, but be warned, they make you pay to enter, even if you don’t park in their lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-9-OrUfrB19o/VB9JRklLUkI/AAAAAAAAJkU/6BGtZ7pmXRw/w537-h716-no/IMG_3665.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J and I hit up some other scenic points. They were nice, but I was tired, and not feeling so well. Fortunately, J took picture duty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Thf3Fx1KeTs/VB9KAKcFcPI/AAAAAAAAJpI/VrBkFNSz3gw/w955-h716-no/IMG_3691.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/--11jUmZu2b0/VB9J3dcDe7I/AAAAAAAAJoM/6w8b-l1FD4c/w955-h716-no/IMG_3686.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We flew back to Maui, since we were departing from there, and checked into our hotel. I was only feeling worse, so we ordered room service. It was my first room service ever. I took a picture, even if I didn’t really eat any of it. :/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-L0gQwEkZRFk/VB9KHcqc6RI/AAAAAAAAL4A/nfZ3Xn7Tf5c/w955-h716-no/IMG_3696.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still feeling ill the next morning, I sent J out to our snorkel reservation. I was bummed I missed it, but his pictures are too amazing not to post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-C5ZA5-W-bGg/VB-pn-hEewI/AAAAAAAALbU/-Kc0N2h_T-A/w1038-h688-no/turtle-head.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-Fflw0h7Hgv0/VB9voVeuy2I/AAAAAAAAJ0k/C_sPgLY_Scg/w1038-h688-no/turtlejon.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We flew home that evening. It was an amazing trip, and we really got to enjoy good weather, and no internet connection (a lovely break from the all the time internet connection we have). J and I definitely hope to go back seeing as we’re closer to Hawaii than NYC now. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-15-2014/hawaii-end.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-15-2014/hawaii-end.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Day 5 - Volcanoes!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a few days in Maui, we decided to hop on over to the Big Island. While there were lava reports on the radio, we didn’t see any active lava. We didn’t think it would be in good spirits to tour on someone else’s devastation. So instead we spent a lot of time at Volcanoes National Park exploring previous eruption sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-FI4O0ZC6V_0/VB9vWUX-wHI/AAAAAAAAJyo/IRAWmfKDdoY/w1038-h692-no/IMG_1168.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We woke up early the morning after our flight to head over to the park. We wanted to start the day by stretching our legs, so, we hiked the Kīlauea Iki Trail to the Thurston lava tube. It’s a 6 mile hike into what was once a lake of lava. Having since dried out, the crater is a great place to explore volcanic scenery. Getting there early led to much more amazing pictures. By 10 am, tons of tourist buses had offloaded, filling the crater.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/8qeoFChDldhfzPzB3fzGqYFORHe0C4at18xwqGRa77U=w524-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned a lot about what happens after a volcanic eruption, and getting to see the rocks and crags up close was great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-WYWjWGiFGro/VB9vgECbLEI/AAAAAAAAJzI/rXAawJudE-M/w477-h716-no/IMG_1195.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J was really into the learning aspect of the crater, and I was really into the making fun of J for learning so much about a crater aspect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/_sLeHtxIGEim-Vqw5G2xjIk1T1Zn36EIWOOrocTl40Q=w581-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though it’s a kind of random picture, a few days before, I had caught a surfboard with my arm while surfing, and had developed a pretty serious bruise. I wanted to preserve it with a photo. Better my arm than my face, I guess. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/P6oRx7G0ZmDhOs2utVWKvX-H9khU3RxxzumJRHE1wN4=w979-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We scaled out of the crater and into the lava tube, where bus, upon tour bus was parked. The tube is a great in and out jaunt, but it didn’t really offer much when compared to the crater. And the pictures inside made my inner photographer cry. With all the flash, poor lighting, and people everywhere, it didn’t lead to great pictures, or a great experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Zc_vJJbFJ7E/VB8vV6SO6tI/AAAAAAAAJOA/ro2vLORrjSE/w955-h716-no/IMG_3524.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After, we drove the chain of craters road. The views were awesome, but the road was more hyped that we’d have liked. It’s a 20-30 mile road that stops where a lava flow crossed the road in 2003, blocking the path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Gm7oRBZz8Z0/VB9vml2pFNI/AAAAAAAAJ0E/wfQUPLYJOEE/w1038-h692-no/IMG_1219.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, we saw our first real lava sighting. We drove to the Jaggar Musuem to watch the lava out of the Halema&amp;#39;uma&amp;#39;u Crater. It was a really beautiful experience. We got in right before sundown, and stayed until sunset. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-bq7B-XPq2sA/VB-UmRfImzI/AAAAAAAALR0/HUnRO8WOK0Q/w808-h538-no/IMG_1119-MOTION.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/10-14-2014/volcanos.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/10-14-2014/volcanos.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Day 4 - Pipiwai Trail!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ughhh. I’ve been sick this entire weekend, and looking at pictures of me hiking and healthy in Hawaii was just too much to handle. But I wanted to get the rest of the trip up on the blog before I lose any more momentum and just start blogging cute exercise clothes I want to buy or something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J and I were last in Hana. Having completed the infamous Road to Hana trip. It was our first (and only) night on the east side of the island. So we wanted to catch sunrise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-FSauXjXzYew/VB-ojuZn_SI/AAAAAAAALVg/PBok97Nk0HM/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0770.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, it was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting up for sunrise made it easy for us to grab an early start. After the sun came up, we headed out to the Oheo Gulch, aka the Seven Sacred Pools. It’s technically an extension of Haleakala National Park, although it only has two trails. The trail down to the pools, and the Pipiwai trail. We did both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-0Dr3qSBlCjY/VB-o5uw9KHI/AAAAAAAALXU/mlyxhqwko60/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0950.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trek down to the pools is short, sweet, and passes by that giant tree you see above. Unfortunately, during our trip, the pools were pretty dry, with only one, maybe two to swim in. If you don’t bring your suit (we didn’t) there’s not a whole lot to see at the pools. It’s a great place to float, relax, and grab a nice tan, but not much else. You can see the swimmers behind Jon’s head in this snap at the pools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-CDezCLEVcLY/VB-o-DtnmxI/AAAAAAAALXo/gfPzABdMwI8/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0998.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we headed to the Pipiwai trail. This is one of those hikes that really makes you wait for the good parts. It was 80 or 90 degrees, humid, and most of the waterfalls along the way were pretty dry. Out of need for shade (and a break from walking on an exposed trail uphill) we stopped to climb a tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-mLGFEyfU9lM/VB-pFHBlbSI/AAAAAAAALYQ/ReaYECKIg74/w477-h716-no/IMG_1020.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a mile and a half in or so (doesn’t sound like much until your ass is sweating, hiking up hill, with no shade). You reach the bamboo forest. When I read about this before going, I was kind of underwhelmed. Like “Woo hoo, what’s so cool about a bunch of bamboo?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-AN6al0HCxBU/VB-pJqZY2CI/AAAAAAAALYk/GYgBh4tlqIQ/w477-h716-no/IMG_1025.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll tell you what! Bamboo sounds like deep, hollow, wind chimes whenever a breeze rolls through. Add that to the fact that our path was shaded, and J and I thought it was the greatest thing ever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It felt pretty surreal to walk through the bamboo though, it’s just not a plant or experience we ever get at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-N5e9UihtbT0/VB-pJ0C3HvI/AAAAAAAALYo/wX2JecS77pc/w1062-h708-no/IMG_1029.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After what seems like a lot of bamboo. You hit the end! Which is this beautiful waterfall. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zWSDob6NLq4/VB-pLv1NOJI/AAAAAAAALYw/_bil7P3IRLo/w1062-h708-no/IMG_1035.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sign we’re standing in front of said to not cross it, or fear getting swept away and dying. However, the current ahead was nothing more than a trickle, so we (and basically the other 20 people who hiked there) went past the sign. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-7IK926oKYFM/VB-pRNkY7vI/AAAAAAAALZM/mqR1kXn5D6c/w477-h716-no/IMG_1050.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the entire falls (with J at the bottom for scale). It was huge, and beautiful. But very very slim. A lot of the falls were almost dry when we visited. And like the pools at it’s base, there were groups of people who came to the falls to swim. So, word to the wise, in Maui, basically, always wear a suit. Or, always be swimming… Or something&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hiked back to the car. Left Hana, and got lunch. We stopped at the Naihiku market and J got the most amazing fried ahi tuna ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-pg45aJCrsgg/VB8mfREAfeI/AAAAAAAALgU/TfEffExsFVA/w884-h716-no/IMG_3325.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t look like much, but the fish was fresh caught, and fried in front of us, and was probably, no joke, the best food we had on Maui. The passion fruit, aka lilikoi, aka get in my stomach best fruit ever, was good too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finished our drive, took some pictures of the scenery (which is beautiful, even if J doesn’t look enthused in the photo below) and went back for a relaxing evening in Wailea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-_HnKkUignm4/VB-pN4YWaOI/AAAAAAAALY4/K_S5ZM3u3fQ/w1062-h708-no/IMG_1058.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-28-2014/pipiwai-hawaii.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-28-2014/pipiwai-hawaii.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Day 3 - Road to Hana!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Road to Hana! Road to Hana! Road to Hana! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to say it’s name too many times, but Road to Hana is one of my favorite parts about Maui. It’s a great reason to get a jeep, take the top off, and drive a few hours down a long windy road that goes to nowhere. (And buy, and consume a lot of banana bread along the way!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-s5Kco6FBw5E/VB-oufZyDPI/AAAAAAAALWo/1sIPJvAu2SA/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0856.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So of course, J and I rented a Jeep (after a lot of begging on my part for a Jeep) and set out early on day 3 to embark on the Road to Hana. It’s a drive that could be done back and forth in one day, but J and I wanted to hike a bunch along the way, and do the Pipiwai trail at the Oheo Gulch. So we decided to spend a night in Hana. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was almost disastrous, as we planned this trip to Hawaii just the week before we flew here. And little did we know, the original day we planned to do Road to Hana, there was a huge foot race/relay on the route. (We’re talking thousands of people running on a one lane road) Thankfully, when we tried to book a hotel, the receptionist told us we were choosing the worst dates for this. Phew.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/NDWzD7LDKbOi2GbZdMLKyZHHkiFU53FG0DhuS5v_ZmQ=w489-h715-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Road to Hana is a journey, filled with twisty passes and one laned bridges, and J and I didn’t want to go it alone. So we downloaded the Road to Hana GyPSy app on our phones. Though the narrator is a little cheesy, without him, we would have never stumbled across things like rainbow eucalyptus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-_ILasbMsR7E/VB-omN9PjoI/AAAAAAAALV4/wa5ecKZL-3c/w477-h716-no/IMG_0804.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-f6Goa6m-3J0/VB-olMsqzqI/AAAAAAAALV0/uOIYvt1i88A/w477-h716-no/IMG_0796.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which are, in my mind, the prettiest trees I’ve ever seen. (Take that cherry blossoms). We also ended up in Keanae. A quiet town with pretty black rock beaches. One of the great things about this narrated, GPS based tour, is that the narrator gives you five important things to do on the road. So there’s no analysis paralysis of trying to pick the best places to stop along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-EPNa5-3laKc/VB91UcXnVnI/AAAAAAAAKXw/cWRt7PIRZow/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0823.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the road, we stopped in Hana. We found a super cute hotel called the Hana Kai Maui (of no relation to the Mana Kai Maui). It was seriously one of the most, clean, modern places we stayed. It felt beachy without having that fake resort feel. And the kitchen was high tech. I wanted to live there forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-EDQooL44HU0/VB92YQvF9dI/AAAAAAAAKeA/mzgYupFIDrU/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0873.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we were on the east side of the island, I hopped into bed as early as possible so I could wake up and catch the sunrise the next day at 5:30 am. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s the last adventure you took?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-24-2014/road-to-hana-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-24-2014/road-to-hana-1.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Vacation Day 2 - Bike Haleakala</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On the second day in Hawaii we were up bright and early to do a 23 mile long bike ride down Haleakala, Maui’s volcano. We booked with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bikemaui.com/&quot;&gt;Haleakala Bike Co&lt;/a&gt; who I would wholeheartedly recommend. Our trip included a van ride to the top, a tour around the crater, and then a long, unsupervised bike ride down. Did I mention unsupervised? (Read: J and I get bored following big groups)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our guide Kemo, was a local who had ridden down the volcano’s roads by bike, skateboard, and even shopping cart. He was hilarious and personable (as every guide should be), and he should basically quit his day job because the man took the most amazing pictures of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YLpt07JEWDc/VB-ogI31ggI/AAAAAAAALVU/UYlXgTuC0Mk/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0711.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We reached the summit (by van, although there were people people biking up the mountain. My legs ached for them) and were able to get out and explore. Kemo took pictures of all the bikers under the sign, and also against the crater view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Q7dGrbZR34g/VB-odGoPSaI/AAAAAAAALU4/kVjHq8xsJuw/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0697.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was nice to stretch our legs, and the tour wasn’t rushed at all. There were a bunch of people starting hikes into the crater, so much so that J and I considered returning to hike in the crater but we never ended up doing so. :(&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-vUqCljSsNTY/VB-ogFnFNKI/AAAAAAAALVM/dmZq7yQr17U/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0719.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Post crater tour, we headed back to where we’d hop on the bikes. You can’t bike down from the crater’s summit, because too many people have died doing it, or liability, or something. So we started a few less-steep miles down the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kemo kept shouting to the back of the van that we were lucky, that days rarely got this clear in Maui. So J &amp;amp; I took about half a million pictures of the landscape. From the higher points on Haleakala, you could see both sides of Maui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BKfNwXv49lU/VBbeVvmFWlI/AAAAAAAAIXg/J4PHOk860rQ/w955-h716-no/IMG_3145.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bike ride was amazing, but simultaneously a little frightening. Some parts of the route are twisty, steep, and have cars driving right alongside you. The brakes on the bike are incredibly sensitive, and very strong, which can lead to unintentional whiplash, but save you from a more awful fate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people were pretty inexperienced at biking, but all turned out fine. Honestly, we did watch one of the other members of our group topple over her bike. A mix of nerves, a large tour bus driving alongside her, and a hairpin turn caused it. She was a little scratched up, but mostly embarrassed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-AzTYoF7PNuw/VB9ztNjylJI/AAAAAAAAKNg/IMPtZoO-4VI/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0738.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the ride was super chill. (this is definitely not a calorie burner) But since we spent a few hours out in the sun, we came back tired and chilled the whole evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-pyq7d7jtB48/VB9zjjf67BI/AAAAAAAAKMU/_P-cs2hSHIc/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0730.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s the longest you&amp;#39;ve biked?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-23-2014/bike-haleakala.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-23-2014/bike-haleakala.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hawaii Vacation Day 1 - We arrive in Maui</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve taken a peek at my Instagram. You may have noticed I was in Hawaii last week! Normally, my boyfriend and I are connected to our laptops all day, every day for work. We wanted to get away from the bright screens, and so we took a laptop-free vacation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J and I left bright and early in the morning, I was super excited and overly awake on the plane while J fell asleep the moment we hit the seats. Fortunately, we scored some great exit row seats so I was able stretch my legs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/643vSB_GhE9l9C7UJzRK2UDbTw3a-WSxEoEKFIrLSpg=w667-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The minute the plane landed, we went to grab a bite to eat. We stopped at Da Kitchen to pick up some local cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bi4cp5quugepcfO5j9NJsKi54VOQfTtzjLFdUAwwoOQ=w587-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite my smile, turns out traditional Hawaiian food isn’t really our thing. I got a pork sandwich, and J ordered a giant Loco Moco (not knowing what a loco moco was, and not knowing that he was ordering the biggest one on the menu). Da Kitchen did a great job cooking our meal, but it was a little too much, and too greasy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To pay for our food sins we decided to start the afternoon off hiking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-fmMhRvAEhP4/VB-pmA6CsSI/AAAAAAAALbk/BRcUUpVNCAM/w1062-h708-no/bestofwaiheejon.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hit the Waihee Ridge trail up around 1pm. Despite everything on the internet telling us this hike would only be good in the morning, or that finding the parking and trailhead was difficult, we had no problem with either. Google Maps saved the day once again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/3GxWU7p8FWWH9p38yPUtsupnU9ZK6ZQ9-KR-dZDmJ78=w496-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ridge trail is basically all uphill, and has a bunch of really beautiful lookout points. Every time I thought we couldn’t gain more altitude, we did! It switches between forested and exposed, and is definitely on the challenging side of trails. J and I loved it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-VaD2BzeHpAg/VB-oUxW8ZeI/AAAAAAAALUA/d5-22uGLMwg/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0578.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the serious climb, the views are totally worth it, you feel like you’re in the middle of a Jurassic Park set. The clouds, waterfalls, and super lush foliage are unlike anything in Northern California. The only thing I’d change? J and I only brought one water bottle for the both of us. We definitely needed two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-8REPgwSmKTU/VB-oZbsPnYI/AAAAAAAALUg/21BC88kBKAI/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0654.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ended the day at the Mana Kai Maui in Kihei. Due to a little switch up with our room, we ended up upgraded into one of their condos. The condo was totally adequate, nothing to write home about. But the balcony, or lanai as all of Maui (and possibly Hawaii seems to call it), was amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-igiayIil4to/VB9yiRsMDBI/AAAAAAAAKF0/NcEN12L-ihw/w1062-h708-no/IMG_0678.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that view, we spent a lot of time on the balcony watching the sunset, the surf, and just chilling. Since the condo came with a kitchen we were sure to grab fruit at the local market. I seriously improved my pineapple cutting skills. I’m a real fruit ninja now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/74r5CwLOW4-ZWpZckwLXx-mp2OYqSQakj5hFjF7dKDM=w1062-h713-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we’re home now! I’ll do some entries over the next few days about the rest of our trip. While vacation is nice, I’m excited to be back into routine. Soylent, running, yoga and work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-22-2014/hawaii-day-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-22-2014/hawaii-day-1.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Upcoming Races.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think all I’ve been doing lately is working, sleeping, and signing up for races.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons I keep signing up, is to keep myself running. So I want to pad out my races to approximately one a month. I&amp;#39;m almost covered until the end of the year. But it&amp;#39;s a little spotty in some places. I like doing races that (generally) don&amp;#39;t require fundraising, don&amp;#39;t have colors thrown at you, or zombies, or photoshoots, aren&amp;#39;t super religious, and are relatively fun. With that said, here’s what I’ve got so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YpDOnJqE-Fk/VBPgFDi14yI/AAAAAAAAIMA/FtNav66dzZ8/w650-h350-no/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-09-12%2Bat%2B11.04.49%2Bpm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://run10feed10.com&quot;&gt;Run 10 Feed 10 - October 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A philanthropic 10k put on by Women’s Health. I’m super excited because I’ll get to run over the Golden Gate Bridge. (I’ve only ever driven under it. Ooops)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-mAseAeTd5H8/VBPgFNSDXII/AAAAAAAAIMI/vfH8SS9S7wA/w650-h580-no/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-09-12%2Bat%2B11.05.21%2Bpm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://theuglysweaterrun.com&quot;&gt;Ugly Sweater 5k - November 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My family’s celebrating Thanksgiving with the ugliest 5k of all. I’m super pumped for this 5k. Both to run alongside (and beat) my siblings. But also because I’ve put together the most hideous Christmas apparel of all time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ABozaaNUJpw/VBPfI5BY7gI/AAAAAAAAILM/kkfAvpWU7OU/w679-h177-no/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-09-12%2Bat%2B11.06.01%2Bpm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.hotchocolate15k.com&quot;&gt;Hot Chocolate 15k - January 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose this race because a 15k is like the lazy man’s half. And I’m lazy. And it’s super flat. And there’s chocolate at the end of it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-PLYtiwGpx90/VBPfJf2VfcI/AAAAAAAAILQ/welfgHWRpFk/w711-h350-no/Screen%2BShot%2B2014-09-12%2Bat%2B11.06.51%2Bpm.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.seawheeze.com/&quot;&gt;SeaWheeze Half - August 15, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I got tickets! A race I love so much, I signed up a year in advance. This was literally one of my best experiences this year. It sold out in under a half hour, but both my mom and I managed to sign up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-12-2014/upcoming-races.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-12-2014/upcoming-races.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soylent so far.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Things have been a little crazy here. Most notably this morning I signed both my mom and myself up for SeaWheeze 2015! Woo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was super excited for it this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/4WtimBfywF1VYbcARzGbXxdfiaif8Z0co0A3F0704Qk=w894-h205-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to recap my experience with Soylent so far. And hit up what I’ve loved, and what I’ve strugged with. Let me give you a week by week of how it’s been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 1&lt;/strong&gt; - Stayed on Soylent all 5 week days. 1200 calories a day on Soylent, uncounted otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 2&lt;/strong&gt; - Horrible stressful week with only 1 day Soylent. Let’s not even talk about my eating habits. (I may or may not have gorged myself on a back of mallowcreme pumpkins.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week 3&lt;/strong&gt; - 2 days Soylent, 500 calories. 5 days muggle food with general moderation.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZU9U9bjti_M/U-zkJH1cDUI/AAAAAAAAIEI/DCMplJYmIRw/w429-h416-no/IMG_2756.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s going on in my blender?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1) I’m recognizing that I have a super weird relationship with food. So when I’m drinking Soylent, it’s helping me get away from some of that. For example, when drinking an adequate amount of Soylent to the point where I’m not hungry. I get this feeling like “I deserve a snack.” Even though I am perfectly satisfied, I’m finding I reward myself with food, even though I didn’t do anything award worthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Soylent, when drinking it, is not unpleasant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) I get a lot more done on days with Soylent. I usually take a brief walk at lunch, clear my head. Finish work earlier, and have more time for activities in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) When I drink soylent, I actively want less food days I’m not drinking soylent.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Not-So-Good:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1) I feel like a jerk turning my team down for lunch daily, or not being able to meet up with a friend after work. I’m not ready to “out” my Soylent habits yet, so a 5 day spread wasn’t working for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Even though Soylent tastes great. I hate the way it smells, makes my house smell, makes me smell. It actively makes me not want to drink it, even though the taste, and general experience is great. I have this mental block before I take the first sip, where I think. Shit, this is going to be horrible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Since meals are provided for me at work, this is actually more effort than not doing Soylent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-uan3B8_4bp4/VAU1KjXdEkI/AAAAAAAAID4/FsGt0Lpv8Vs/w963-h716-no/IMG_3009.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food I&amp;#39;ve been wanting to eat with coworkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as you can see from my little week break down. I’m shaking it up and doing a 5:2 split. (5 days off, two days on). Which I may move up to a 4:3 split once I get back from vacationing in Hawaii next week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the most important thing is to find a sustainable way to incorporate this into my life. Honestly, the 5 days on spread, it wasn’t fitting my lifestyle. So I’m trying a method that mimics intermittent fasting more. I’ve liked it (so far) more than fasting, because Soylent even at low calories, takes away any hunger or cravings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s been working for you so far?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/9-10-2014/soylent-so-far.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/9-10-2014/soylent-so-far.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cleaning out my closet.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Getting things done over this long weekend. My closet has been the ultimate mess since I moved in. I bought these cheap wire storage bins to store clothes. Spoiler alert, they didn&amp;#39;t work. So I spent today re-doing my closet/dressing area. First order of business, get a real dresser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went to Ikea, even though every time I build a piece of their furniture I promise myself I will never ever go Ikea again. But then they&amp;#39;re so cheap and easy that I forget the building hell, and I keep coming back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-g8mbbk9_2XQ/VAPVRIDirUI/AAAAAAAAH9k/GM_4Gdd_rRE/w896-h672-no/http---makeagif.com--media-8-31-2014-8JH_Pl.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Final product. I still need to hang some things for more color!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/6xr0VUll_dZSV4rIKJX7S-gR6WTKYaDA-GQ6bnDXp2I=w561-h672-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any fall cleaning planned?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-31-2014/closet-clean.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-31-2014/closet-clean.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seawheeze Weekend - Race Recap!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back at SeaWheeze, my only wish is that I would have taken more pictures. Because, the more I think about it, the more I realize, everything we did there was beautiful. Our B&amp;amp;B (O Canada House) was this amazingly cute Victorian, with fancy plated breakfast, yummy pastries, cute puppies, and the sweetest owner. The weather was perfect all 3 days, the scenery was gorgeous. Really, you couldn&amp;#39;t have asked for a better weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I&amp;#39;m not perfect, so I mostly gawked at everything around me, and didn&amp;#39;t snap near enough photos. After my mom and I hit up the Showcase Store, we went to pick up my race package. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/K0COu1cmh3Hs31a86jn8F_fWN80FTY_1Fa_J_6N3dhM=w668-h672-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talk about no line, we waited maybe 5 minutes to get to a booth and grab the goods. My favorite part of the pack? The Chip Wilson race chip. And the water bottle that we got as swag. I was pretty tired from the early morning, so after getting everything we went back to the B&amp;amp;B, grabbed breakfast, napped, and walked back to the convention center to check out (but not participate in) yoga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/XTH938gCtrZco3VsTXWPxJyCFGAdV6fDU4WL9MfM3_I=w875-h672-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was surreal to watch a few hundred people doing yoga in the open air. As much as I wanted to join, I&amp;#39;m kind of glad I didn&amp;#39;t. I am out of yoga practice and would have been sore the next day. Which I&amp;#39;ve heard isn&amp;#39;t good when you&amp;#39;re running a half marathon. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of. The next morning, I woke up at 4:30 (again...) to get in line for the half. Since it was my longest run ever, I was incredibly incredibly nervous about doing things right. I was nervous about eating at all before the race, and ended up just having a piece of pumpkin bread before heading over to the convention center. I took a picture in front of the brunch sign before running, so I&amp;#39;m pretty sure I didn&amp;#39;t deserve anything yet. (But at least I looked good at this point.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-piiEleVflbs/VAFfqPTSJ0I/AAAAAAAAHys/hNLWjrrhgwE/w446-h621-no/seawheeze3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were led through a really rousing warm up of jumping jacks and other light exercise. Unfortunately, the warm up was at least 50 minutes before my wave (1:10) made it to the starting line. So I&amp;#39;m not sure it helped much other than to get me in the spirit of the run. It was super easy to find the pace beavers, and they pumped us up, and gave the whole wave tattoos to help track our times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-vzR8vdAkztU/U_jP9OilNcI/AAAAAAAAHiQ/-UDU7R2l-oo/w537-h716-no/IMG_2893.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I&amp;#39;m bad at kilometers, so this wasn&amp;#39;t very useful. But it did stay on, despite all the sweating. I was able to keep pace with the group until about mile 6. Where I started to falter. And by mile 9, I was ka-put. I was a little bummed, but since I had kind of slacked on my long runs right before the race, it&amp;#39;s really what I should have expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, the race was a lot of first timers half marathoners, so I wasn&amp;#39;t the only one who got tired around this point. The worst part of faltering early was that the last few miles of the race are gorgeous. Runners are weaving around Stanley Park. But at this point all I was focused on was FINISH THE RACE and DON&amp;#39;T DIE. So I hardly paid attention. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mom was the best cheerleader though! She caught me at 3 of the cheering stations. Unfortunately photographing runners is both hard, and super unflattering. So here&amp;#39;s an okay looking back-shot of me and quite a few other runners going around the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-LWw4Cc_78u4/VAFfp5BMnFI/AAAAAAAAHzA/RiCrw690Prs/w446-h639-no/seawheeze-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But! I did finish, without medic nor dying. And coming in at 2:29 means that I&amp;#39;ll definitely PR SeaWheeze 2015!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-29-2014/seawheeze-half-marathon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-29-2014/seawheeze-half-marathon.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seawheeze Showcase Store Recap</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the lack of updates. Between Seawheeze, and coming back to a lot of work. I haven&amp;#39;t really had time to update. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seawheeze was amazing, I loved every minute of it. But I can&amp;#39;t lie, the reason I originally signed up for the half, was to get a crack at the showcase store. You see, Lululemon puts out a bunch of limited edition merchandise for the race, and getting one of a kind yoga pants was basically my dream come true. But, honestly, I felt kind of guilty just flying out for new clothes. So I signed up, and trained (a little less than I should have) for a half marathon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my re-telling of the showcase store. Fair warning, this is pretty much the reason I decided to run this race, so I have some serious bias.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mom also came out for the weekend to cheer me on, and she&amp;#39;s pretty much down for everything, so when I told her about the store, she was all set to wake up at 4:30 am and head over. It was an early morning, but we got into a very nice corralled line at 4:45 am. At this point there was still a lot of space, approximately 40-50 people in line total, with chairs and blankets everywhere. We brought a blanket, spread out, chatted with people next to us, and chilled until 6 am. Despite it still being dark out, everyone was amazingly friendly, and I met so many great people. It made me feel less like a crazy person knowing others were up at 4 am too. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/RDyOwbhlZ50QcI2Y5Qd9L151ymaq_Rfl2Prn70ujffk=w608-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to say, getting there right before 5 was clutch, because at 5:00 am, the line started to really heat up. The whole queue probably doubled to about 100, if not 150 people by 5 or 5:15. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At around 6:30, the line was all the way around the convention center. (I know because I had to pee. My suggestion, hop into the Fairmont hotel near by. Almost all the guests are runners, and honestly, we all looked alike.) But when I came back Lululemon had hired had all these cute characters, who were walking around, chatting with the line. Sorry for the potato quality of my photos, my iphone and lack of sleep combined didn&amp;#39;t help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/iP6kUEs-mbVbcu9oQRLk-GomOZDyQC9TgDr6yv4fIS8=w406-h715-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While waiting, my mom and I heard horror stories from other people in line about how in previous years, there was no limit, so the goal was to grab everything in your size. So originally, we planned to divide and conquer, just grabbing everything we could find in both sizes. The doors started opening at 7 am. And they had a volunteer/worker at the door clicking down the amount of people they let in each wave. Fortunately, we were the first group in, and everything was set up beautifully. Each area had little balloons marking the size of that area. So we abandoned our grab each other everything, ran to our respective sizes, and started grabbing stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/KzA9FhUij5IV_m1SJuJ6jtGfpbHUhP46BjMp5NMuYQE=w1056-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My suggestions here. Take everything you think you might want. Duffel bags went within the first group. Know your sizes, because it can be hard to grab product after people have ravaged it. But ultimately, have fun. This felt like the best shopping spree ever. I was like a little kid in a candy store. After we grabbed all the things we wanted, we heaped them down in a pile and started sorting our top 15. We came to our choices pretty quickly. Tried a few things on for size (mostly scuba hoodies and coats) and checked out. The process was easy, flawless, and we were on our way in about 20 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/soXta8Wjm7PgZDYlEza3FBl5cVVcae6OsSVau40Jo7o=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/B_hHhpBgXZgF-9VZxYT1Ic3_zuzcREad0uzClTW3U8U=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later that afternoon, I talked to some girls at the wonderful B&amp;amp;B we stayed at. They arrived to the store after a run at around 7, and waited in line for over 2 hours, and a lot of stuff was sold out. While they thought our morning sounded crazy, personally, as an early riser, waking up two hours earlier than them, and waiting for the same amount of time, seemed worth the amazing stuff we got. Overall my haul looked like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/f3_Deex7zhgaTtTjDfYiiacITZ_Rk30nceJnLdPY3Ro=w955-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really focused on the rainbow swirled pattern, and the graphic dark lines for the pants. I plan on taking some more individual images of different pieces later this week. The showcase store was an amazing experience, and was coordinated so well. It was a great way to meet other runners, and a really exciting start to the weekend. My mom and I both maxed out our 15 pieces, and I&amp;#39;ve really loved the stuff I got. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Race recap soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-28-2014/seawheeze-showcase-store.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-28-2014/seawheeze-showcase-store.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seawheeze Weekend</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Spending the weekend at the Lululemon Seawheeze half marathon. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be back soon with updates!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/1pFrqmxxngscNxjjK4tDXkkBBh5nDoRgKdkteatvIeY=w708-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-22-2014/seawheeze-weekend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-22-2014/seawheeze-weekend.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Knitting night</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m learning to knit, and projects like this always inititally frustrate me because I&amp;#39;m not perfect at them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now, I look at my running, or biking. When I started those, I was so slow, and so awkward. Lately though, I&amp;#39;m fast, and I feel good when I do it. So I try to remember that the same thing is true of everything I do in life. I&amp;#39;ll be bad at first, and then eventually, and very very slowly, improve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My starter scarf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-4J2qVKLz4zo/U_LVf75O1EI/AAAAAAAAHYA/xqd2H6PqAbk/w913-h716-no/IMG_2831.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;My project&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My teacher&amp;#39;s much more advanced scarf&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/wtvaNSOxNIP9-rqHhNsQVKGOaJKRKlUbTv4DN7zdMms=w640-h715-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-18-2014/knitting-night.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-18-2014/knitting-night.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Weekend Down!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I survived an incredibly busy crazy weekend off Soylent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To try to maintain some social life, I’m not drinking soylent from Friday night to Sunday night. It allows me to still indulge in regular food, crazy activities, and life without a blender bottle strapped to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most adorable things I ate this weekend:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-1BMoGda3Bt8/U_F4jUYsskI/AAAAAAAAHVc/znTwOUaT5xw/w643-h716-no/IMG_2822.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In more exciting news! J’s coworker got married this weekend, which called for a lot of celebrating. The wedding was north of the city in San Rafael, aka Sun Rafael because it’s soooo much warmer. The ceremony was a balmy 90 degrees, but the reception cooled down to a sweet 70. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crossing the bridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-YqOT7uD9EE0/U_F4JLABPcI/AAAAAAAAHVk/lxuzv6mGO6M/w724-h716-no/IMG_2798.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting dolled up for the wedding&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/bxyFfctvb8984eW_zgHGV7hZ0UOtxakyD2DSx71K1G4=w517-h715-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The oak the ceremony was held under. The theme? Love grows here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-E697lsRoop8/U_F4PWaJO8I/AAAAAAAAHVs/WCikAEsF7JA/w654-h716-no/IMG_2801.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite amped up image of the couple&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/4Ho_Pf_wxE3D_EnDXuh8QDLGgrlUygCNp6b61tuwZ2k=w583-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, this weekend, Soylent taught me how much extra I’ve been eating. I felt more uneasy eating full meals, and I’ve been noticing the heaviness of certain ingredients (sugar, sugar, sugar). My stomach gets upset when it gets to a level I would have considered full just a week ago. And I find myself taking slower, smaller bites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, spending a week on soylent makes everything taste more flavorful. Spices are hotter and more complex. Cuts of meat seem much juicier. Produce is almost unreal after four days of an unarguably bland liquid. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had mixed feelings about returning to my Soylent only diet tomorrow. Part of me is incredibly excited not to have to think about food. It complicates my life a lot. But another piece of me is sad to give up on all the flavors, tastes, and overindulgences I’ve had this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve definitely seen a trend down in my weight over the days I’ve had Soylent, which is unsurprising and also wonderful. I’m hoping this mix of soylent and “normal” food will continue to work for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-17-2014/first-weekend.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-17-2014/first-weekend.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The good old wall pantry.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I live in a teeny tiny apartment, my kitchen is probably the size of a lot of people’s closets. And as such, there are only a few small cabinets for storage. So when you receive 40 pounds of food at once, you have to, as Tim Gunn would say, make it work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This wall has become my make shift pantry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-SxnftEyBGXY/U-zkSJ4PMrI/AAAAAAAAHLs/_-aN1l9n0NE/s716-no/IMG_2763.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Soylent Wall&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had no idea what to expect size wise with soylent. And so, I shipped soylent to myself at work, (it would have gotten nicked from my door), not realizing that each week is about 10 pounds. So I’m delivered this pallet of soylent that I have to haul down stairs, across the parking lot, and then up to my apartment. When I finally made it to the apartment, I was covered in sweat and basically looked like a cartoon character shoving my soylent up the last few steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of work, I have a favorite mirror for selfies there. I love it, it’s super flattering, and really really large. But the situation’s a little awkward, because in order to maintain looking professional amongst my coworkers I have to make sure I snap the picture when no one else is there. So I’m always awkwardly looking around making sure the coast is clear and then posing like an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-3FKZ1F2WPw0/U-0KEZVxRtI/AAAAAAAAHPU/ggaEZpMlO1o/w440-h716-no/IMG_2771.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Dramatic mirror seflies&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend is so crazy. I have a friend coming to stay with me for 2 weeks, and she missed her birthday. So I wrapped up a bunch of small things. Then we also have a wedding, an ikea trip, and a bunch of touristy stuff to drag my buddy to. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m never going to get any sleep!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ecU9-hR8-II/U-2UqhAbVUI/AAAAAAAAHPM/HlfSHmU6prQ/w617-h716-no/IMG_2777.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;So many presents&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s your weekend looking like?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-14-2014/wall-pantry.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-14-2014/wall-pantry.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don’t cry over spilled milk, a broken elephant or a flat tire.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I almost cried over two out of three of those today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll fill you in. I have a huge crush on Jonathan Adler. I don’t even know what he looks like, or if he’s a good person. But I love his designs. So when he came out with a cheaper department store line, I bought a ton up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I had to ship it to my new apartment, and in the process, one of my favorite pieces, an elephant lamp shattered. :( I’ve been super glue-ing him back together, but I’ve had to glue so much, I ran out. Here he is in a mostly fixed state. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DkiXGQnn_L0/U-uOF9toaII/AAAAAAAAHCc/JmSyqfB2evk/w837-h716-no/IMG_2724.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then today, on the way to work, I got a flat tire on my bike. Which seemed okay, because I had a tube and pump at work. So I worked at replacing the tube (I’m a total bike fixing novice, this took me basically forever), after many attempts to pump my bike, I found out the needle was broken, so the new tube won’t even inflate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here was a glory photo from when I thought I fixed it. Haha. WRONG.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/6ghX3zG0Q0a58C0eR-EJHKXSITQEi6rSTgHfdROCIDA=w567-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, my day was amazing. I took a beautiful walk at lunch and came across the most bizarre 80’s style fitness track. You can walk around and stop at all these little stations in the woods to work on different skills. I skipped the fitness stations, but eventually I want to come out and play with the rings station. One of my dream goals for life is to be able to do a pull up, and it could be fun to do some aerial skills on this thing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/loAPNvxCXKdujF5v10SSvcMQfggSCx50DhhmToaDzKs=w567-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soylent today has been good. It’s hard doing an experiment on yourself. Like I’ve felt a little eugh when it comes to digestive issues. Fortunately, I have yet to become a noxious gas machine like some drinkers report. (Knock on wood). But I definitely felt a little on edge today. However, two of my coworkers went home sick. So is it a stomach bug? Soylent? Guess I’ll find out in a few days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-63QYJDPwtOc/U-uQM0rbulI/AAAAAAAAHGY/n8WIgvAJfuE/w548-h716-no/IMG_2727.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My batch today tasted the best yet though. Getting good measurements on a food scale has helped a lot with that. (Since I don’t want to drink a whole 2000 calorie bag). And actually, this is probably disgusting, but I don’t mind it luke warm. I chill it overnight for whatever reason, but I actually kind of enjoy it after it’s gotten back to room temperature. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever, I’m crazy. Hope everyone else’s day went better than my own. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-13-2014/broken-elephant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-13-2014/broken-elephant.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soylent Day Two, as told in selfies.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been making my daily batch of Soylent the night before. I’ve heard letting sit, makes the liquid less gritty, and also, it gives me more time in the morning to get ready. I’m lazy, so I just measure, blend, and then shove the entire blender in the fridge for the night. (minus the base, guys, I’m not an idiot.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing this means I can wake up, re-blend for a second to reintegrate the oils that have separated (delicious) and go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry in advance for all the selfies. After yesterdays photos, I needed a lot of make up and good angles in today&amp;#39;s post. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/CBPIJcl_0fF156E36fX72nMsovGURT9_nj8CHpo-Wb4=w715-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;Kay plus blender&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day two was as easy, or easier than day one. I actually have a hard time finishing all the soylent by the end of the day. I need to drink more in the morning, because before Soylent, I most naturally ate the most during the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/X7WEWJiQj3U3FK0prUDv7JoAQ5CWblBWoAbV4EnI2bs=w903-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;soylent in blender bottle&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, no one in person has noticed or asked me about my kind of bizarre eating habits, which is really relieving, because honestly, I don&amp;#39;t really want to explain. My suggestion for keeping it under wraps? I&amp;#39;ve been able to fit it all in a blender bottle, which you can see in basically every picture. So it&amp;#39;s pretty small and inconspicuous. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I&amp;#39;m still worried, I can&amp;#39;t avoid lunch with the coworkers forever. Lately, I&amp;#39;ve been hoping to do non-eating activities during my normal lunch break. I figure walking, and yoga can replace my usual munching. Unfortunately, the last two lunches, I’ve just been doing work at my desk. Uggggh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-u2nb_4jLKjk/U-pS_OfZHMI/AAAAAAAAHAk/4ZrTT4QX3gg/s716-no/IMG_2705-MIX.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Quad selfies&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall though, I feel even, and happy not making choices. The last two days have been fairly stressful, and usually that would mean I’d be chomping my way through snacks and coffee at work. But I haven’t. I mean, I still drink coffee, tea, and other nearly 0 calorie beverages. But I’m not trying to binge my stress away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s silly but, I want magical results at day two, so then I’d feel like I have something great to tell you, or to write about. So far, I haven’t exercised heavily since drinking soylent, but I’m hoping to do a good run tomorrow and see how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-12-2014/soylent-day-two.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-12-2014/soylent-day-two.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Soylent Day One!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Before I tried Soylent, I read about it everywhere. As much as I could. But reading about it was unfulfilling because all of the descriptions are so bland… so neutral…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I get it now! When I got home, it was almost easier to describe what Soylent wasn’t, than what it was. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-6mLCc2lqXWo/U-mSipjQmTI/AAAAAAAAG78/nEnEh1WTcLA/w955-h716-no/IMG_2689.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Measuring my day of food&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like, you know how when you eat food, and it’s your favorite food. The way you eat is happy, the act of consuming is an exciting moment. And you&amp;#39;re like super happy. In your eating. It’s a good food experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But like, you can also have really bad food experiences. You can eat something gross, or something you’re not in the mood for, and you honestly don’t want another bite. It’s a negative food experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soylent is neither of these. I found myself taking sips to keep myself from getting hungry (something I quickly noticed if I got too focused in my work and forgot to drink). But I was neither repulsed or excited to eat more. It’s pretty late at night and I’m only a little more than 2/3rds of the way through 1000 calories of Soylent. But I just sip at it every 20-30 minutes or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did eat real food today though to ease in. Two apples. One first thing in the morning, and one at 5 pm. I want to make sure my digestive tract doesn’t freak out on me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall it went, well. No reason to be nervous. Granted, everything is easiest the first day. Everything but posting these pictures!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-anY_c5mfPPw/U-mW0P0Z0DI/AAAAAAAAG8M/BWOnKWwdhCE/w922-h532-no/kittstart.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate putting these late night “Before” pictures up, but I want to track my progress and see how soylent affects my overall body. So pardon the awkward photos we snapped at midnight last night. But hopefully, these not so sexy shots will lead to some great afters. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total today ~1240 calories&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-11-2014/soylent-day-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-11-2014/soylent-day-1.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Anticipating Soylent</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I love the feeling of anticipation right up until I have to take the first step. During the morning, I dream about running, until I hit the moment where I need to lace up my shoes and take off. When I’m just ready to go, I hit that initial dread of the activity. What if it goes wrong? What if I hate it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it’s no surprise that now, the night before I embark on a primarily liquid diet, that I feel that ache in the pit of my stomach. Unboxing soylent. Beautiful. Showing the packaging off to my boyfriend, amazing. But as I go to eat my “last supper”, I feel uneasy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-vbQMTypmDZw/U-TvStzUjUI/AAAAAAAAGzY/DDZ_OMWWWSc/w647-h716-no/IMG_2648.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;My starter kit&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I received my shipment of soylent last week. And because I’d like to pretend my life demands fanfare, I refused to begin a liquid diet on a Thursday, because as any yo-yo dieter knows, diets must begin on a Monday, to give you the entire weekend to binge and feel bad about your choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soylent comes in a ~2000 calorie pack, and advertises ideal nutrition. As I’m a woman, and relatively sedentary, I plan on experimenting with my calorie intake until I find a good medium. Ideally somewhere between 1000-1500, depending on my activity levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-jmBYPGGJJ-o/U-TvekpiidI/AAAAAAAAG1E/bbXrywTLfqA/w850-h716-no/IMG_2657.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;One ‘day’ of Soylent&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this said, I’m still a social person, and I plan on eating normal food over the weekends so my boyfriend isn’t driven insane by my food experimenting, and hopefully so I can’t ruin my digestive system (and other body systems?) too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least I have until tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/8-10-2014/anticipating-soylent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/8-10-2014/anticipating-soylent.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lake Shasta Caverns - Shasta day two!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After a hot sweaty hike the day before. We opted to get out of the heat, and hide in the caverns of Lake Shasta, where temperatures are much much cooler. Getting to the caverns was pretty low activity, you bought a ticket, walked down to the dock, got on a boat, went across the lake, and then were bussed to the cavern. Despite being sedentary, the views were amaaazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-LhdmCPXMdnA/U-K-11IrUuI/AAAAAAAAGTk/lww3P8YEOVI/w955-h716-no/IMG_2480.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Views of Lake Shasta&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inside the cavern was really amazing (granted, I haven’t really been in many caves). The guide was well rehearsed, and went by a kind of cheesy script that kept the children, and the adults with no attention span paying attention, and away from touching all the rocks. (Which is bad.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-EzpepRdzDsY/U-K_MHPAXiI/AAAAAAAAGWY/ZBI-ZV7F0II/w537-h716-no/IMG_2497.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since people online make a big deal of it, we were hoping the cave might be strenuous. But it’s really mostly sight seeing. We were told it was 80 stories of stairs, but in reality, it’s 80 steps, or 8 stories, and when moving in a group, you basically take this at a snails pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole cave is pretty amazing, but the best part is the end, with this crazy kind of cathedral formation at the end. This was the only time the guide really paused, and so we were able to convince him to snap a quick picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-TxellRnmXsM/U-LEBhcyuMI/AAAAAAAAGfI/0fbq9wkmoUM/w537-h716-no/IMG_2541.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;J and Kay in da cave&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-TOH1y134b9s/U-LARVT4RZI/AAAAAAAAGds/hPqcNNvXs3g/w537-h716-no/IMG_2535.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/7-27-2014/shasta-caverns.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/7-27-2014/shasta-caverns.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Castle Crags - Shasta day one!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This summer our vacations have been beautifully formulaic. We choose a place a few hours out from San Francisco. Book a shitty motel in the area. Then hike, bike, and eat the local food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since day one in SF, J has been wanting to go to Shasta. So bam! We did. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-5IiGWdT2Upg/U-K9vta2UkI/AAAAAAAAGOQ/DAkb-vXkHRE/w537-h716-no/IMG_2442.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;We made it!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-gGut2AlXKqI/U-K8JvIqWlI/AAAAAAAAGFo/i4soP8Met8U/w537-h716-no/IMG_2393.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Rocks!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because we are nowhere near cool enough, we decided not to actually hike Shasta itself. Mostly since we wanted to spend our time just looking at it. And also because, it takes like a whole day, and it was 108 degrees outside. So hot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ended up at Castle Crags, a pretty sweet hike. We started from a parking area, and climbed. Since we believed the things we read on the internet, we hear this was going to be a 5 mile hike, total. Unfortunately, since we never looked at a map, we didn’t realize that it was 5 miles to the top, and 5 back down. Oops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/Ec8vG2XtRLxBrsHopGNMB6vn09VLzOxqTkPV25TtZ5I=w1062-h682-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-IOobemrRHlQ/U-K8Au5rl_I/AAAAAAAAGEg/3MUvXsnSovo/w955-h716-no/IMG_2387.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hike had about 2000 ft elevation gain over a 5 mile windy path. And then the last 500 feet was a lot of scrambling up rocks. Which I pretty much hate the most ever. I always feel, regardless of how much actual safety there is, that I’m going to fall down. So after a few minutes of scrambling, I told J to go ahead, and I’d wait. I was tired, it was hot, we were running out of water. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-Y8PdFkfn1xo/U-K9gaSGoaI/AAAAAAAAGMw/aAIbmjvNGvE/w403-h716-no/IMG_2431.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;J summits crags. Balla’.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He made it to the top, it was amazing and beautiful, and I’m still glad I didn’t go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, on the way down, we stopped at this small, .2 mile hike to Indian Springs. Where there was potable water! I have never been so happy in the world ever for potable water. It was beautiful and amazing, and the best thing ever. We drank a lot of spring water, and then ran down the mountain for 5 miles. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a shower that flooded the entire bathroom. But I must say, a crappy motel bed and threadbare blankets never felt so good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/7-26-2014/castle-crags.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/7-26-2014/castle-crags.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fourth of July the Works</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m not a firework person. I’m not an America the beautiful person. I don’t get most rah-rah holidays to begin with. But I went to the local fireworks with family, and I took some cool pictures and have to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1C8ZLrBs_Q4/U-K5azQXM8I/AAAAAAAAF04/_upJ65ewzsg/w537-h716-no/IMG_2259.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;‘The works’&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though people camped out at the venue all day to get good seats. We arrived like 30 minutes before show time, and snagged great digs right where a funnel cake vendor was closing. (Note to friends, and hey, even enemies. Don’t watch how your funnel cakes are made. I would quicker eat mixed concrete.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show was set to music, which was actually pretty awesome, and they timed the explosions to hit key points in the songs. There were even little heart fireworks for a song about love. Unfortunately most were upside down, but it’s the thought that counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite taking about 120 fireworks pictures with my iPhone, none contain the heart. Cool story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-tMmF3a6y9a4/U-K3D1BrSAI/AAAAAAAAFjo/hKx8pK1y-lY/w537-h716-no/IMG_2167.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All together, it was actually pretty cool. Even if it meant I had to listen to Katy Perry’s firework song like 20 times. I was a huge nerd and took a bunch of pictures, filmed the entire finale, and said “oh my god” way too many times. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows, maybe I’ll come around on the Fourth of July. Might be my favorite holiday next year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/7-4-2014/fireworks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/7-4-2014/fireworks.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Berries in the Bay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was little, my family used to go apple picking every fall. We’d ride the hay ride, pick more apples than we would ever eat, and buy a dozen apple donuts. I now realize this tradition was more for getting to binge on apple donuts than a love of picking apples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last weekend, J and I went to go relive my childhood by picking Olallieberries (a cross between a bunch of berries, most notably the blackberry) from a small farm down highway 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-QPtW6iX8xO0/U-K1s5_qJiI/AAAAAAAAFZA/wTdZn39DjvI/w955-h716-no/IMG_2094.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Kay picks berries yo&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were (are?) like children. (And of course, we were the only people there without children, go figure.) We ran around trying to pick all the “best” berries. J kept telling me we had enough, we had too many berries, we would never eat this many. And I was pretty sure I could finish all of the berries in the car ride home. (Spoiler alert: I did not eat all the berries on the way home.) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-OIZ9vwBLmzs/U-KwwXP8vyI/AAAAAAAAFWI/a3nQdR0jkzA/w955-h716-no/IMG_2082.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Serious berry haul&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our serious berry haul, we made our way to Henry Cowell Redwoods State Park. A mouthful of a name, if you ask me. We started aimlessly walking around because we couldn’t find a map, and then ran into an ultra marathon trail run group, who were on their 35th mile. I then felt a little guilty about my long runs being 6 miles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/CBgpwsm27tnbWLWhgB8PO8XYpIv5oOCh9jBQLqHBGXc=w578-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;But for real, it’s beautiful&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since we had no destination, we eventually hit a river that cut off our path. The ultramarathoners were unreal amazing and just ran through the waist deep water like it was nothing. However. I was unprepared, so J and I scrambled across the rocks to get to the other side. Success! Our shoes only got a little wet, and I didn’t fall in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-dyp46wIbqfo/U-K2YQrQBzI/AAAAAAAAFeQ/f4SlRyv4ukI/w537-h716-no/IMG_2122.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;This is a river&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, after crossing the river, we came upon a bunch of dead animals in the woods, and that seemed like a good sign to turn around, so we did. We hopped back in the car, drove home, and ate all the rest of the berries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should have picked more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/6-21-2014/berry-picking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/6-21-2014/berry-picking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lazy Bear, the ultimate eating experience</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever find something decidedly cool, from an incredibly uncool place? J and I found out about Lazy Bear, an underground dinner you sign up for lottery style a few months ago. After months of putting our names in, we finally were chosen for this many many course experience. We thought we were cool, and hip, and maybe read it in the New York Times, or heard it from a food loving friend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But no. It was Yelp. The number one rated “restaurant” in SF. Not so cool. The courses were all amazing, and there are so many, that I won’t describe every one in detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-GC2xJUp4KII/U-Ku5cqjisI/AAAAAAAAFMQ/6BxIMi2tENM/w537-h716-no/IMG_2021.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s begin. I missed snapping photos of some of the initial courses, so, this is not representative of the full meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-A0mkZkZN9A4/U-Kun0Ymk1I/AAAAAAAAFKI/kWSOLu_mbbI/w537-h716-no/IMG_2010.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A tomato water and jalapeno gel with an oyster in it, and a bite stolen. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-YB4Z5j8-Hm8/U-KurgEzjdI/AAAAAAAAFKs/KIf9e_XC0F4/w537-h716-no/IMG_2013.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A high end take on “chips and dip” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-UaTc6eoyER8/U-KushEDoEI/AAAAAAAAFLA/aDTSZZYc7JQ/w537-h716-no/IMG_2014.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soft shell crab with the most amazing sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/nKInhmhiZ9oxf9cuekUT6yP0uMnXnJXVBzOeFe1L-gE=w688-h716-no&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Homemade brown butter bread, with a side of homemade butter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-art7NxwYc2g/U-Ku61pH9HI/AAAAAAAAG3Y/mqlKd1UZWS8/w955-h716-no/IMG_2022.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some sort of fish with compressed fruit on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-y76u1ifIlEY/U-KvDsKWh1I/AAAAAAAAFNA/sFIDWvhd8b8/w537-h716-no/IMG_2025.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rabbit charcuterie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-L7dj77MR1MI/U-KvJ_8Au6I/AAAAAAAAFNk/2AdMpAzYJlM/w955-h716-no/IMG_2028.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A take on congee with peas, abalone and cucumber&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-709Xl26z-lU/U-KvYzr4q-I/AAAAAAAAFO8/7HgY-aBZi4k/w955-h716-no/IMG_2035.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Squab. Yum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-p_WsKHEKOqI/U-KvcpNZHII/AAAAAAAAFPk/chQNi1g_S4s/w955-h716-no/IMG_2038.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steak sous vide. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-6rgq2T8YAAc/U-KvhxoUg1I/AAAAAAAAFQY/aaUOAKNcWBw/w955-h716-no/IMG_2042.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deconstructed pie with bruleed stone fruit and meringue sides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-FX-Os6Z5Mfo/U-Kvletd_sI/AAAAAAAAFQ8/debhFQzBC20/w955-h716-no/IMG_2045.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sorbet and chocolate dessert&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-drAl7e9qH0s/U-KvmTfZzyI/AAAAAAAAFRI/FTOSUWe-ErQ/w537-h716-no/IMG_2046.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some bites to end the meal on, at this point I was stuffed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/6-9-2014/lazy-bear.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/6-9-2014/lazy-bear.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ziplining is for adults too!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our second day in Lake Tahoe, we didn’t want to kill ourselves with another hike, especially since we were snowed on the day before. Buuuuut, we both wanted to see balancing rock before we left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We considered a few activities, kayaking, paddle boarding, zip lining, all the watersports were closed until Memorial Day. I really, really didn’t want to zipline. I thought it’d be super boring, since we did it in Costa Rica. But I caved in, and let J book it. We ended up getting a two for one deal though, and hell, I like coupons. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-MF3Q5JJ772c/U3G58nAFtFI/AAAAAAAABAA/wM2F13TCXSY/w1059-h706-no/kitt-glamour-rock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-p2Wu5OSegmM/U3G5t6LhPFI/AAAAAAAAA-0/L9mBHjTelr8/w1059-h706-no/dino-rock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;J’s knees hurt, and it didn’t look like the gate to balancing rock was open. So we parked in a little outlet nearby. OMG. Best decision ever. It was like less than half a mile to the site. We ran around and took pictures. Since the rock entrance was closed, we were the only people there. Which made for a quiet morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-U05o7E1MZaQ/U3G59ZWoQ7I/AAAAAAAABAE/mtXwFnpk--0/w1059-h706-no/kitt-holding-rock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-I-9NhpYICGg/U3G5xy2Zy_I/AAAAAAAAA_I/KNh6gF3reDw/w477-h716-no/jon-climbing-rock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you’re at balancing rock though, it almost feels like it could fall on you. It didn’t, but it feeeeels like it could.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-9qpPDSp4cHA/U3G5yQN2ExI/AAAAAAAAA_M/1FmU55iCiUM/w1059-h706-no/jon-holding-rock.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-9BQes_JxnJo/U3G6CSF3H2I/AAAAAAAABAs/b1_KVMZ-llU/w477-h716-no/kitt-muscle.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of things falling, I’m the clumsiest person ever. I totally bit it and fell hard on my hands and knees walking back to the car. At the time, it didn’t seem like a big deal, you know? I just fell. I’m an adult. I should be able to handle it. But as we got on the road, I realized that I was bleeding through my yoga pants. We picked up some bandaids and alcohol wipes and cleaned up before getting to the high ropes course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-i3orpttFHkk/U3WlqtTCPYI/AAAAAAAABDs/x5iwFnu546A/w504-h672-no/2014-05-11+13.42.47.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dude. It was insane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me first point out that we were the only childless adults at the facility. But once we got past that, it was so cool. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-F_vh07mAtTA/U3WlrlNLctI/AAAAAAAABDU/fxL5zrvrpx4/s672-no/2014-05-11+15.11.44.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, they rigged up 5 different levels of treetop courses. They all involved some level of balancing, climbing, jumping, and zip lining. You would clip in and climb up a ladder, onto a platform, have to tightrope across to the next platform, and then skateboard in mid-air into a weirdly woven web that you climb across to a zipline. And repeat with a billion different challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-vfE1FnLv0nI/U3WlqBLu4UI/AAAAAAAABDE/arS7FNkUljk/s672-no/2014-05-11+14.32.30+HDR.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did every single one of them. It was crazy fun. This was also the Sunday of Mother’s Day, so there were a lot of moms there. I felt really bad at some points because a lot of the moms, despite being in decent to good shape, were really afraid of failing at the courses, so they didn’t even try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-2V7j8TJf0EM/U3WlrE5onqI/AAAAAAAABD4/awH9-tJZTIY/w896-h672-no/2014-05-11+13.56.19.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be fair though, it was hard. The next day I was so sore, I wanted to puke.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/5-13-2014/moms-day-in-e-bay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/5-13-2014/moms-day-in-e-bay.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tahoe Adventures. Or how to get both sunburn and hypothermia in the same day.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When you’re not living near your mom, but all your friends are booked for mothers day, it’s a sweet time to go away. J (the boyfriend) and I decided to head up a few hours north to Lake Tahoe to get active. We weren’t traveling in style by any means. We stayed in a sleazy, but incredibly cheap motel. Despite kind of being a baby about these things, I have to admit, it wasn’t actually that bad. It barely cost us anything. And though the room smelled of stale smoke, and our blankets were a little thin and ripped, we barely spent any time here, and the cost cutting was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-ALSpo8GhuWg/U3G6BswcjqI/AAAAAAAABAc/yCWLKuDD7_s/w1059-h706-no/kitt-jon-emerald-bay-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;K &amp;amp; J at Emerald Bay&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wanted to do a bunch with our weekend away. We expected a big hike and some kayaking. It was supposed to rain day one, but it was only a 20% chance, so we decided to risk our giant hike on the first day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hit up Emerald Bay. My favorite hike so far in Tahoe. It’s a little C-shaped bay with gorgeous mountain views, rock formations, and a formidable waterfall. My advice, don’t even plan to park near the trailhead. On our way to the trail were so over-excited when we saw the top of the waterfall and the gorgeous scenery that we spent a ton of time before even getting to the trailhead to get pictures. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-7XMMRnZaJz0/U3G54uBbo0I/AAAAAAAAA_0/_GgdAPETEYA/w1059-h706-no/kitt-emerald-bay.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kitt at Emerald Bay&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-vmsdh8wRBns/U3G6CrBx5ZI/AAAAAAAABBM/3cEAwTKPc58/w1059-h706-no/kitt-top-waterfall.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;So many pictures of Kitt at Emerald Bay&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started the descent from the parking lot to the trailhead around 1pm, and took even more time to play around photographing the waterfall that was half a mile away. Despite a disappointing winter, there’s still enough snow melting to sport a raging falls. Armed with a new camera, and a lot of energy from morning caffeine, we spent an hour playing around with shots in the falls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-8FrHiYUeBPU/U3G5ptYPomI/AAAAAAAAA-Y/u5EXIuhmAn4/w1059-h706-no/artsy-waterfall.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waterfalls!&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-zaNoDJUZX3o/U3G52VZqqxI/AAAAAAAAA_c/8WB1168HRo8/w477-h716-no/kitt-artsy-waterfall.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waterfalls!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day was beautiful, it was a brisk but sunny 50 degrees. We started on what we planned to be a 12 mile hike, out to the next state park (D L Bliss) and back. Emerald Bay is beautiful, you see amazing coastal views, hike a slightly variated trail, and enjoy the mountains and the bay. It’s not a hard trail by any stretch, just long and a little windy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-1E5SI_WcDXc/U3G-1CLYXgI/AAAAAAAABBc/pJtpDINsxqM/w896-h672-no/laketahoecollage.png&quot; alt=&quot;Collage of all my pictures !&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few miles in, the sky started to drop these tiny balls of snow. It was like being showered with little dippin’ dots. We thought this was adorable, and funny. J and I figured, it’s better than rain. The little ice balls just bounced off us as we walked. Note to self, if it starts precipitating, don’t continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZRAe8SbZ74I/U3G_Tc2YPVI/AAAAAAAABB4/hUXa0Y1tXlk/w504-h672-no/2014-05-10+16.16.14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;J in snow&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got to the half-way point, 6 miles in, and snow started just pouring from the sky. It was so thick, you could barely see a few feet in front of you. Armed with only hoodies and athletic pants we trekked back. It was adventurous and stupid. We became walking snowmen, with snow sticking to our hair and cotton clothes. At some points it was like hiking through a snow globe and at other points we felt like we were stuck in the arctic.  The last mile, my body was wet with a miserable mix of sweat and snow. But looking back on it, despite the cold and the snow, it was worth it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-ZaVky7eMOKI/U3G_T3_8wiI/AAAAAAAABB8/6YjDIrkLo40/w504-h672-no/2014-05-10+16.14.23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Walks in snow!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But of course, as soon as we got to the car (and brushed all the snow off of it). The sky cleared up, and the day went back to 50 degrees. At least we didn’t get snowed on day 2. :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/5-12-2014/emerald-bay-day-1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/5-12-2014/emerald-bay-day-1.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello Hello Hello... Aloha</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Living in SF gives you more of an excuse to jet off to Hawaii. It&amp;#39;s closer than New York, Boston, and Florida, and despite crossing an ocean, you don&amp;#39;t have to suffer through customs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went recently on a three day &amp;quot;work&amp;quot; trip. Which is to say that work paid for the trip, but I (nor my teammates) didn&amp;#39;t actually get any work done. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team stayed at the Kaanapali Westin in Maui. The resort was kind of faux exotic. When you entered there was this giant manmade waterfalls that they had trapped a variety of wild birds and koi in. So that when you exited checkin you were greeted by flamingos and macaws chilling under a giant waterfall. It&amp;#39;s definitely bizarre, and seemed a little trying too hard. (But yo, I still took pictures of it)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-o3xOnhPnJgc/U2V-pR5S8QI/AAAAAAAABsU/7nkH5-WUNKc/w924-h693-no/14+-+20&quot; alt=&quot;Crazy entrance way&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hawaii is a vacation spot that doesn&amp;#39;t take much work if you&amp;#39;re coming from the mainland. Everyone speaks the same language, your GPS works, and you don&amp;#39;t really have to do much to have fun. While it&amp;#39;s nice for relaxing, it can be almost too effortless. Given the lax environment, I spent a lot of my time walking along the beach, reading outside in perfect weather and just chilling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/bkLyvPG8l9eJeGIYPaDa4UaROPbUO6vBbJFiuZt2QoU=w934-h693-no&quot; alt=&quot;Collage of Hawaii&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just recently moved to a new team at work, and wanted to impress my coworkers and meet people. So I probably tried too hard. I was extroverted, stayed out late, danced, introduced myself to everyone and basically made sure I met everyone. It was a nice mix of work (meeting everyone in the world, omg.) and play (laying on the beach and people watching)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-dfQ179ICuGs/U2V-pZFIDwI/AAAAAAAABsg/3HcsFC3keyY/w924-h693-no/14+-+27&quot; alt=&quot;View from my room&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately I got in my two favorite things in Hawaii, Acai Bowls (omg, learned to make these at home. Going to eat them forever.) and Surfing (also should do this at home, buuuuut.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/5-4-2014/hawaii.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/5-4-2014/hawaii.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cataract Falls, or how to climb the Eiffel Tower of San Francisco</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A week or two ago we had a completely open day. The weather&amp;#39;s been great, and so we wanted to get outdoors and try a new trail, stretch our legs out a bit from a long week of screens, screens and more screens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the boyfriend and I hit up Cataract Falls. When we got there it was chilly. Like, when you live in California, sometimes you forget how cold it can get. We planned the hike around a 6 mile loop that promised coastal views and ended at Cataract Falls. The coastal bit, honestly, was just so boring. Basically no elevation change, gentle weather, and mediocre views. It would have been just as good to walk on a track, or in a mall, god.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-l-G2xUF9wVI/U02toZo_udI/AAAAAAAAAQM/SmToLc4_m9I/w955-h716-no/14+-+20&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five miles through, and with way too much energy left, we made it to the falls area. Not tired, we decided to tack on an extra 5 mile loop to the hike to get to the base of the waterfall and back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we took off, running down the falls trail, jumping down stairs, speedng through straight paths. I had that nagging feeling you get in the back of your mind, &amp;quot;Hmmm, this seems like a lot of downhill.&amp;quot; But, like an idiot, I ignored the fact that I was basically hurtling my body down a mountain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-jj7eWdlnkg0/U02toc6YQcI/AAAAAAAAAQo/yzTdVWoy93Y/w537-h716-no/14+-+16&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The water was gorgeous, and made up for our lack luster hike. But fuck man, we had to climb all the way back up. 1,400 feet elevation to scale, basically 140 floors to tackle. Initially, I was dying, and expected to vomit, curl up and die (I think my boyfriend was embarrassed of me at this point. Haha). But after the first few &amp;quot;flights&amp;quot; of steps, my body just stopped caring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, it sucked the whole way up. I was a disgusting sweaty mess. But I stopped taking breaks and just pushed through the bulk of it. I felt pretty bad ass. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-BZk_KutFwlo/U02toXyfGyI/AAAAAAAAAMQ/1jaox2je8G0/w955-h716-no/14+-+25&quot; alt=&quot;Alt te&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got to the top and thought we were basically done with the loop, but we still had a mile and a half to go. Longest mile and a half of our lives, we were cold, tired, and our quads were ready to fall off. When we got to the car, all I wanted to do was sit, forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ended up ordering in and just chilling, accomplishing nothing more than a super steep 10 mile hike that day. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kaybueno.com/4-24-2014/cataract-falls.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kaybueno.com/4-24-2014/cataract-falls.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>